{"cards":[{"mId":"961e744a-39d7-4558-bde7-b81e58808ef9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a holiday where you purchase the travel and accommodation together","mBack":"package holiday"},{"mId":"7f3ac1d6-f3c3-450a-99da-3ceab324cc4c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an extremely beautiful view","mBack":"breathtaking view"},{"mId":"21752d8b-e4cd-4ff4-b1f3-b2cd778b0a33","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a cheaper form of flying than a scheduled flight","mBack":"charter-flight"},{"mId":"ec390912-2034-4207-ad86-a2ccc0b260c1","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the place at the airport where you register for your flight and deposit your luggage","mBack":"check-in desk"},{"mId":"d3765ddf-75e0-47d6-a86a-26ca97fd6417","mCardType":"text","mFront":"where you wait for your flight to be called","mBack":"departure lounge"},{"mId":"e8797cb0-1da2-4a3b-96cb-c3ad97390615","mCardType":"text","mFront":"somewhere a long way away","mBack":"far-off destination"},{"mId":"74751a75-5028-489b-a02e-64178c4b78cf","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to take a holiday to escape a busy or stressful lifestyle","mBack":"to get away from it all"},{"mId":"eb5dfc6f-9fae-4c71-b096-3e523739eb27","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an organised group shown around a place of interest by an expert","mBack":"guided tour"},{"mId":"03ec7008-7817-4c39-b373-cc5bd631c84f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a glossy publication with details of holiday packages","mBack":"holiday brochure"},{"mId":"58d842c0-1eee-438d-bb54-b3cd37dfa164","mCardType":"text","mFront":"where you go for a holiday","mBack":"holiday destination"},{"mId":"6c7e0faa-e174-4f2c-ad92-0c165136c2ff","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a special holiday that you are unlikely to repeat","mBack":"holiday of a lifetime"},{"mId":"5a7ac2aa-f2fc-4b90-8232-8724400eb747","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a place where lots of people go for a holiday","mBack":"holiday resort"},{"mId":"0dc0770a-e0ef-4174-8926-5fb9817e49b8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"crowds of tourists","mBack":"hordes of tourists"},{"mId":"0a9ff328-1258-4b8b-a444-a3d60a6ab7a6","mCardType":"text","mFront":"objects produced locally","mBack":"local crafts"},{"mId":"c37fa187-e9d8-46fb-9099-bcbf8f22e96e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"an extended weekend holiday including Friday or Monday","mBack":"long weekend"},{"mId":"fea047ea-8c40-419d-a119-447849d29404","mCardType":"text","mFront":"outside of the main holiday period","mBack":"out of season"},{"mId":"7565a5da-3e48-40fb-8d3d-84dbcf070704","mCardType":"text","mFront":"very pretty village","mBack":"picturesque village"},{"mId":"a0ede3c3-2f27-440b-b49a-8842ad383e9d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"the place where your passport is checked","mBack":"passport control"},{"mId":"ff5e6e50-e177-4e42-bc97-754175b1c8da","mCardType":"text","mFront":"sites of interest to tourists","mBack":"places of interest"},{"mId":"ff423ce1-9cb0-4bed-b3fc-99d84af94a48","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a holiday, often in Africa, to observe wild animals","mBack":"wildlife safari:"},{"mId":"e301eb9e-1bcb-4b69-a287-f165f8131932","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a holiday where you supply your own food","mBack":"self-catering"},{"mId":"8b9570db-3332-44c6-93ec-d4cf107ed75d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a short holiday","mBack":"short break"},{"mId":"7d6e2a7b-a482-487e-add2-01036067f07d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to look around the tourist sites","mBack":"to go sightseeing"},{"mId":"671b6c6c-ce5f-476c-94d7-3c1b53e6ef41","mCardType":"text","mFront":"extremely beautiful countryside","mBack":"stunning landscape"},{"mId":"3a7773b3-f9ed-47b0-b5fa-f585f7b9b1dd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a shop that specialises in booking holidays","mBack":"travel agent"},{"mId":"7581ba18-5401-4037-b0e5-2982c3f4c68c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"somewhere where too many tourists go","mBack":"tourist trap"},{"mId":"f3893215-6d27-4d24-ad51-960285f97a68","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a cheap form of accommodation","mBack":"youth hostel"}]}